Guide to Dean's Office Records Collection RG.051
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Dean's Office Records
1953-2018
1990-2013
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
RG.051
114 Linear Feet
Biographical / Historical
The NYU Polytechnic School of Engineering dates to 1854, when the NYU School of Civil Engineering and Architecture as well as the Brooklyn Collegiate and Polytechnic Institute (widely known as Brooklyn Poly) were founded. Their successor institutions merged in January 2014. Note that the Dean's Office records from pre-2014 use the title "President" while records from post-2014 use the title "Dean".
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was transferred from the Dean's Office in Summer 2017. The accession record was updated in 2023.
Arrangement
This collection is housed in sixty-eight boxes and maintains original order. The container list was created using the Dean's Office records' original folder names.
Scope and Contents
The Dean's Office Records Collection contains documents from 1953 to 2018, with a bulk of documents from the mid 1990s to 2010s. These records were assembled by the Dean's Office before and after the NYU-Poly merger of 2014. Note that the Dean's Office records from pre-2014 use the title "President" while records from post-2014 use the title "Dean". The collection includes real estate development records, marketing/recruitment documents, and academia-related University records. The collection is 114 linear feet, located on bay 27, shelves 2F-7A.
Polytechnic Institute of NYU; Polytechnic University (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.).; Merger - NYU-Poly - 1973; Universities and colleges -- Mergers -- New York
- Bernie Bulkin, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Gerald Dawes, 2007-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Charles Fabrikant, 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Richard Fishbein, 2006-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Randy Frey, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 5)
- William L. Friend, 1986-2006; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 6)
- William L. Friend, 2007-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 7)
- William L. Friend, 2010-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Sunil Godhwani, 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Robert Gold, 2013-2014; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Charles Hinkaty, 1997-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Michael Kappaz, 2001-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 12)
- William Kramer, 2007-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Paul Horn, 2004-2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Paul Horn, 2008-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Christine Ianuzzi, 2011-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Lawrence Katz, 2006-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Jeffrey Lynford, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Jeffrey Lynford, 2012-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Jeffrey Lynford - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Jeffrey Lynford - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Jeffrey Lynford - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Jeffrey Lynford - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Jeffrey Lynford - 2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Jeffrey Lynford - 2001-2007, 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Craig Matthews, 2006-2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Craig Matthews, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Craig Matthews, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Craigs Matthews 1995-2006, 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Craigs Matthews 1995-2006, 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Mark Ronald, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Michael Ruiz-2015, 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 1)
- John P. Schaefer, 2000-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Ronald Schloser-2014, 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 3)
- James Smith, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Joseph Steinberg, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Robert Tsao, 1998-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Philip Venables, 2013-2014; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Fred Wilson, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Rudolph Wynter, 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 9)
- NYU 2031, 2008-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 10)
- NYU-Common Days, 2008-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Briefings, 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Middle States Commission on Higher Education, 2007-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 13)
- External Meetings/Updates, 2008-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Internal Meetings/Updates, 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 15)
- NYU Development, 1993-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 16)
- NYU Global, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 17)
- NYU Other, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 18)
- NYU Shanghai, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Toward Becoming a School of New York University, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 1)
- A Year of Historic Progress, 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 2)
- A Year of Historic Progress, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 3)
- NYU Schools, 2008-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 4)
- NYU Venture Fund, 2010-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 5)
- CICU Materials, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Uri Komornik Case, 2004-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 7)
- FEC Kunhardt Case, 2006-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Yaniv Ravee, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 9)
- The 156th Commencement Exercises, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Ji Mi Choi, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 4, Folder 11)
- The 154th Commencement Exercises, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 1)
- The 158th Commencement Exercises, 2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 2)
- The 155th Commencement Exercises, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Robert D. Dalziel, 1990-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 1)
- David Dibner, 1983-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Mario Cardullo 2007 - 2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Michael R. Corey, 1993-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Ursula Burns, 2003-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Mario Cardullo - 2010, 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Mario Cardullo - 2009, 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Henry Bachman, 1987-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Israel Borovich, 2005-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Glenn Britt, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Linda K. Jacobs, 1992-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Violet Jacobs 2008 -, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Joseph & Violet Jacobs 2000-2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Shelley A. Harrison, 1994-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Leila Heckman, 1998-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Michael Hora, 1997-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Jacob's Family Foundation, 1995-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Ruth Fattori, 2005-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Richard Foxen, 1988-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Rachelle Friedman, 1995-2006; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Patrick Garzillo, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Clifford Goldsmith, 1984-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 12)
- James Oussani, 2002-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Stewart G. Nagler, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Robert J. Myers, 1991-2003; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 3)
- R. William Murray, 1987-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Arthur C. Martinez, 1993-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 5)
- John Kirksey, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Michael O'Brien, 2006-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Laura Parsons, 2002-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Leonard Pomata, 2007-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Robert Prieto, 1998-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 10)
- John G. Puente, 1994-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Steven M. Rittvo, 1997-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 12)
- David Schweiger, 2006-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Leonard Shustek, 1995-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Henry Singer, 1986-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Dennis Dintino 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Joey Colelli, 2006-2022; 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Kurt Becker 2010-2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Kurt Becker 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Sharon Albert, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Executive MGMT. 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Executive MGMT. 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Executive MGMT. 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 8)
- CORE - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 9)
- CORE - 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Harry Wechsler, 1980-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 11)
- CORE - 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Donald Weisstuch, 1999-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Paul Soros, 1983-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Jerome Swartz, 1995-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Casimir Skryzpczak, 1986-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Dennis Dintino - 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Barbara Hall, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Liz Lusskin 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Liz Lusskin 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Erica Marks 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Erica Marks 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Richard Thorsen 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Richard Thorsen 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Robert Ubell 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Robert Ubell 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 10)
- UG Academics 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 11)
- UG Academics 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Grad Academics 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Grad Academics 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Freshman Innovation and Tech., 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Admissions 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Assoc. Provosts, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Athletics 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 18)
- NYC Acre 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 10, Folder 19)
- BEST CTR. 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 1)
- NYC Acre 2011, 2010-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 2)
- NYC Acre 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Middle States Association, 1988-2003; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Middle States Association Self-Study Workshop Baltimore, MD, 11/28/90, 1990; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Middle States Dinner-3/14/93-6:00pm, 1993; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Commencement Ceremony 151th-157th, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Poly / NYU / Aby Dhabi Plans, Strategy, UCL Material, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Items of General Poly Interest, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 9)
- NYU Brochures and Catalogues, 2011-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Poly / NYU Strategic Planning July - 2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 11)
- The 157th Commencement Exercises Polytechnic Institute of New York University, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Item 1)
- College Presidents Summit, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 11, Item 2)
- Middle States Self-Study Steering Committee, 1991-2000; 114 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 1)
- ABET (#4), 1996-2003; 114 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 2)
- ABET Visit 10/20-22, 2002, 114 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 3)
- ABET Draft Statement of Visit Dates: November 17-18, 2008, 2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Middle States Responses, 2002-2003; 114 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Middle States, 1974-1987; 114 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Middle States, 1988-2002; 114 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Middle States Binder, 2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 12, Item 1)
- ABET (#2), 1993-1999; 114 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 1)
- ABET (#3), 1993-1999; 114 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 2)
- ABET (#1), 1988-1989; 114 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 3)
- ABET Meeting, 1990; 114 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 4)
- ABET Meeting, 1990; 114 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Catt (#3), 1991; 114 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Catt, 2005-2006; 114 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 7)
- article "Capturing the Unicorn", 2005; 114 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Polytechnic Amendment of Charter, 2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 9)
- NYU Poly Africa Relationship, 2006-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Advanced Energy Res. & Tech. Ctr., 2007-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 2)
- AERTC. 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 3)
- AERTC. 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 4)
- AECOM, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Admissions - 2007, 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Admissions - 2008, 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Admissions - 2009, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Administrative Council - 2010, 2005; 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Adelphia, 1998-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 10)
- ABET 2005 - 2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 11)
- ABET - 2009, 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 12)
- AITU - 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 1)
- AITU - 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 2)
- AITU - 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 3)
- AITU - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 4)
- AIG, 2006-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 5)
- AITU - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Alumni Corres. 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Alumni Correspondence 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Alumni Corres. 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Alumni Corres. 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Alumni Events 2011-, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Alumni Events 2005-2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Alumni Association General, 1994-2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Alumni Board, 1994-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 14)
- AMCF (John Furth), 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 15)
- American Council on Education (ACE), 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 16)
- ASEE, 2007-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Ashoka, 2006-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Asian Universities 2009 -, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Articles - 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 4)
- ARUP, 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Articles 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Articles 2011 #2, 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Architecture for Humanity, 2005-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 8)
- ANSI, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Bojan Angelov, 2007-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Angel Fund, 2006-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Amity University, 2009-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Asian Universities, 2005-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Asian Universities - 2004, 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Asian Universities 2000-2003, 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Assistant Support Network, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Assoc. Governing BDS. 2010, 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Assoc. Governing BDS. 2007-2009, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Athletes - 2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Athletics - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Athletics 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 9)
- AT&T, 2005-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 10)
- AURP, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Bar-Ilan, 2007-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Tony Bastardi, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Bear Sterns, 2006-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Brooklyn Chamber 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn Chamber 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Chambers 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Chambers 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Bridge Park, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Borough President, 2007-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Academy of Music, 2008-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Brookhaven National Labs, 1998-2006; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 8)
- BMCC, 1994-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Booz & Company, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Bob Bonnelli, 2006-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Board of Education, 2005-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Big Data, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Best Center 2005 - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Best Center - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Best Center - 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Richard Bendis, 2008-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Kurt Becker 2007 - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Carnegie Corporation, 1974-2020; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Career Services 2010, 2010-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Campus Connect, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Charles Camarda, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 4)
- George Bugliarello, 1990-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Bucknell, 2010-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Bklyn Tech Triangle, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Brooklyn Nets, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Bklyn Navy Yard 2006 - 2008, 2006-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Bklyn Navy Yard 2009 -, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Brklyn is Hot, 2000; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Brooklyn Historical Society, 2006-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Brooklyn Chamber 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Brooklyn Community Foundation, 2006-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Case, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Catholic Community Issues, 2005-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 2)
- CATT - 2009 -, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Center for Mathematics and advanced Supercomputing, 1994-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Center For National Policy, 2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Ctr. For Tech & Education, 1996-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Ctr. For Urban Future 2010, 2007-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Center For Urban Future, 2007-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Central Party School 2010, 2010-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Central Party School 2007-2009, 2007-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 10)
- David Chang 2010 -, 2010-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 20, Folder 11)
- China - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 21, Folder 1)
- China - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 21, Folder 2)
- China - 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 21, Folder 3)
- China - 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Tim Chen, 1996-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 21, Folder 5)
- CBS - 2008, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 21, Folder 6)
- CBE - 2008, 2008-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Chase Manhattan, 1988-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 21, Folder 8)
- David Chang 1994 - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 21, Folder 9)
- China - 2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Civil Engineering 2008 - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Civil Engineering 2010 -, 2010-2013; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Cisco, 2009-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 4)
- CICU 2005 - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 5)
- CICU 2011, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 6)
- CICU 2012, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 7)
- CICU 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Christmas List, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Ji Mi Choi - 2008, 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Ji Mi Choi - 2009, 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Ji Mi Choi - 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Ji Mi Choi - 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Ji Mi Choi - 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Chinese Academy of Sciences, 2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Chinese Academy of Eng., 2005-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 16)
- CASB, 2008-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 17)
- China Institute, 2011-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Comm. On Higher Ed. 2010, 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Comm. On Higher Ed. 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Comm. On Higher Ed. 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Comm. On Higher Ed. 2013, 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Commencement 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Marge Colloff, 2008-2009; 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 6)
- The College of Management, 2005-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Collegeboard, 2007-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Colleges & Universities - 2001 -, 2001-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 9)
- College Alliances 1995-2000, 1990-2000; 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 10)
- College Alliances 2001-2004, 2000-2004; 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 11)
- College Alliances 2005-, 2005-2012; 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Cold Spring Harbor, 2007-2008; 114 Linear Feet (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Commission on Higher Ed. 2009, 2009-2010; 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Commission on Higher Ed. 2008, 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Commission on Higher Ed. 2005-2007, 2004-2007; 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Commission on Higher Ed. 2004, 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Commission on Higher Ed. 2003, 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Commission on Higher Ed. 2002, 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Commission on Higher Ed. 2000-2001, 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Commission on Higher Ed. 1994-1997, 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Commission on Higher Ed. 1998-1999, 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Communications - 2012, 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Communications - 2011, 114 Linear Feet (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Communications - 2010, 2010-2011; 114 Linear Feet (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Communications - 2008-2009, 2008-2010 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Community Board 2, 2005-2012 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Computer Science & Eng. 2012 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Computer Sci. & Eng. 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Computer Science & Eng. 1994-2009, 1994-2010 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Con Ed, 2006-2012 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Consultants - 2007 -, 2007-2008 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Consultants - 2006 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Consultants - 2005, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Convocations (Yearly), 2010-2012 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Convocation - Oct. 22, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Council on Foreign Relations, 2007-2012 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Council on Compet - 2010 -, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Correspondence General - 2009 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Correspondence General 2010 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Correspondence General 2011 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Corres. General 2012 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Correspondence General 2013, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Correspondence Incoming - 2009, 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Correspondence Incoming 2010 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Correspondence Incoming 2011 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Corresp.Incoming 2012 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Correspondence Incoming 2013, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Corp. & Foundation Rel. 2010, 2010-2012 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Cornell, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Cooper Union, 1996-2012 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Convocation/inauguration, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Davidoff Malito 2008 - 2009 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Davidoff Malito 2010 -, 2009-2012 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- CUSP 2010-2011, 2011-2012 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- CUSP Jan. - June 2012 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- CUSP July - Dec. 2012 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Cushman & Wakefield, 2009-2011 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Andrew Cuomo, 2009-2011 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- CUNY, 2006-2012 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Michael Crow, 2008-2012 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- DHL, 2011-2012 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Dennis Dintino - 2009, 2009-2010 (Box 28, Folder 2)